2 Russians, 2 Jews, and a Puerto Rican walk into a bar...
Caught Stealing is a crime, thriller, comedy film directed by Darren Aronofsky.
Burned-out ex-baseball player Hank Thompson unexpectedly finds himself embroiled in a dangerous struggle for survival amidst the
criminal underbelly of late 1990s New York City, forced to navigate a treacherous underworld he never imagined.
Hank Thompson, played by Austin Butler.
Detective Roman, played by Regina King.
Yvonne, played by Zoë Kravitz.
Russ, played by Matt Smith.
Lipa, played by Liev Schreiber.
Shmully, played by Vincent D'Onofrio.
Caught Stealing is a 2025 American black comedy crime thriller film directed by Darren Aronofsky and starring Austin Butler as a former star
baseball player-turned-bartender who unwittingly runs afoul of New York City's criminal underbelly while pet sitting for his neighbor.
Regina King, Zoë Kravitz, Matt Smith, Liev Schreiber, Vincent D'Onofrio, Benito
Martínez Ocasio, Griffin Dunne, and Carol Kane appear in supporting roles.
The film is based on a 2004 novel of the same name by Charlie
Huston, who adapted it for the screenplay.
The film's score was written by Rob Simonsen and
recorded by the British post-punk band Idles.
Produced by Columbia Pictures in association with Protozoa Pictures, Caught Stealing was
released in the United States by Sony Pictures Releasing on August 29, 2025.
The film has received generally positive reviews from critics, with
particular praise for Butler's performance and Aronofsky's direction.
The film was a moderate success, grossing $32.5
million against a $40-65 million budget.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel or
book, cat, baseball, criminal underworld.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.